extramirchi.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy - extraMirchi.com

Privacy Policy for http://www.extramirchi.com/

At extraMirchi.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This page outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://www.extramirchi.com/ and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, http://www.extramirchi.com/ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies**

This blog is monetized using Google AdSense and various other affiliate links. Google AdSense, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet, including the display of [more relevant ads](http://www.thepicky.com/google/how-google-adsense-interest-based-ads-works/). Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content [network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Chitika , kontera, etc,.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://www.extramirchi.com/ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

We has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://www.extramirchi.com/’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Links:**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we extramirchi.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.extramirchi.com/contact/).
